

# MARÍA MEDINA

#### www.mmcprojects.dev

medinamaria90@gmail.com Phone: 603595370

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a software developer with +7 years of experience in the finance sector. Proficient in back-end development and Linux consoles. Currently studying at the renowned 42 programming school, working as a freelancer and building my own web apps with Django.

#### **SKILLS**

- Programming: C, Python, PHP, Javascript, bash, linux.
- Web develoment: Django RF, Flask, SQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, React, APIS.
- Automation of work processes
- Financial Skills: Debt management, accounting, taxation, cash flow analysis
- Excel: Financial modelling, macros, building models from scratch.
- Self-learning: Highly focused on expanding skill set
- Communication: Experienced in client interaction, providing solutions

## **Work Experience**

Back-end developer Freelance projects (Dec 2022 - Current)

- Developed and deployed complete web applications using Python (Django or Flask), MySQL (SqlAlquemy or ORM), JavaScript & Bootstrap. Expecience working with Django API Rest framework Check my projects at my portfolio.
- Built a web scraping tool for a SEO company to track keyword rankings and automate data collection, saving a lot of time to SEO technicians.
- Colaborated with a renowned author to develop its website (www.currocanete.com). Successfully implemented an online academy within the website. Using Wordpress, PHP, Javascript, HTML and CSS.
- Worked on various projects involving C language, Python, and other technologies.

Financial Analyst with python (Nov 2020 - Dec 2022) Urbania International (Real Estate), Málaga, Spain

- Developed and implemented complex financial models for Residential Development, Build-To-Rent, co-working, PBSA and Equity lending. Data analysis and model automation with Python.
- Monitored investments. Reported to international funds investors through regular communications.
- Assisted in financial Due Diligence for M&A transactions.
- Tresury forecasting for investment decisions and capital calls.
   Utilized Python scripting for data extraction and forecasting calculations

Financial Controller (Feb 2016 - Nov 2020)
Celeo (Energy transmition & Generation), Madrid, SPAIN

- Provided accounting and tax control for the Spanish renewable energy portfolio projects. Administered cash flow forecasting and equity financing.
- Consolidated financial statements and managed auditing processes. Reported financial models, cash flows and debt covenant to fund bondholders.

Accounting & Finance intern (Feb 2015 – Feb 2016) Enerfín Sociedad de energía (Elecnor Group)

Co-Founder and administrator (Jun 2018 – Feb 2021)

Mundo Orenda NGO (www.mundoorenda.org)

### Education

Dual Bachelor Degree: Business Administration & Laws Universidad de Córdoba | Spain

Masters's Degree in Economical and Financial Management CEF Estudios Financieros | Madrid, Spain

**Computer Science** 

42 Programming school | Málaga, Spain